There are always two truths!
I'm Detective Juri!
Yay! It's started!
Today, let's go find our target.
Where is it? Here?
Is it here?
The target is here!
Let's go!
You worked properly
!
It's Av or
there
is Although
It's cold.
Is there anything new?
I think I did something
You were dancing something
What?
Oharu is 20 years old?
Is it called dancing?
Have you ever changed yourself?
Have I ever changed?
What?
I don't remember this.
Don't try to change it.
I heard a word in the brief.
What?
Oh, that's why you're 20 years old.
I'm 20 years old.
I was talking about something else.
We'll tell you why we came to you,
20-year-old Oharu.
First of all, let's reveal the truth.
It's the second time we've met.
It's my first time.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
It's the first time, so I don't know
how many months it's been.
Thank you for waiting.
So, you're 20 years old.
Don't you have any worries?
I'm still a kid even when I'm 20.
I don't feel like I'm 20 years old.
Let's not forget our childlike spirit
even when we're 20.
My legs are getting tight.
Freedom.
You're 20 years old, so you're worried
about your looks.
I have a problem.
I wore the same clothes as I was 20
years ago.
I couldn't see my face.
I'm 20 years old, so I'm worried about
my looks.
I want to see it!
I think it would look good on you if
you wore it on TV.
I think it would look good if I wore it
on TV.
But if I wear it on my body...
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm wearing a beautiful costume.
I see.
You said good things.
You're right.
You're cute.
I'm crying.
I solved the problem.
I haven't been able to give you any
special information.
I'm sorry.
I solved the problem with this.
I want to ask you what you enjoyed
recently.
What I enjoyed recently?
I want to know what you were absorbed
in.
I made a pepperoncino modoki the other
day.
I searched for a simple lunch on the
Internet.
The pepperoncino modoki was delicious.
I fried bacon, garlic, and cod roe and
mixed them with pasta.
I thought it was a good idea.
If you mix pasta with something, you
can make a round pasta.
I thought I could make pasta.
That's great.
Please make it perfect.
I'll make potato pasta next.
What kind of potato pasta?
I'll put a lot of potatoes in it.
I'll make it sweet.
Sweet pasta?
It might be like a mogura.
I see.
There is a dessert pizza.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm waiting for it.
It's a way to make a deal.
I hope you'll be satisfied.
I'm satisfied just to have you two.
I'll make a souvenir for you.
What is it?
Show me.
I'll do it.
Let's open it.
It's a present.
Don't draw eyebrows.
She's an adult.
What's with the sun?
When you become an adult, you can
forget about childishness.
You're good!
Thank you very much.
I put two of these on my desk.
I put them on my suitcase when I went
on a trip.
Really?
Yes.
I gave you a sticker saying,
put it on your suitcase.
No way.
You look fashionable.
I'm not fashionable.
You are fashionable.
You are not fashionable.
You haven't put anything on your
suitcase yet.
I haven't.
You are going to put a cute sticker on
your suitcase.
What is this?
It's a cute sticker.
A cute sticker.
Let's go.
I hope you put a sticker on your
suitcase when you meet someone.
Bye bye.
See you.
Please cut out the Juriaki talking 15
seconds ago.
Bye bye.
Look at this.
This program is a program where six
people who are active to promote
something exciting challenge various
things to raise the excitement barometer
in the world.
I will prove the exciting future.
Happy New Day
Let's go.
Hello.
Good morning.
News.
It's a new segment.
Today's guest is Kanami.
Today, I'm going to introduce you to
the sparkling eyes of Kagami's tear
bags.
So, I invited her as a guest.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please introduce yourself.
There is someone who needs to introduce
my sparkling eyes.
Let's welcome her.
Ms. Yoshikawa Hiyori.
You're introducing me without my
permission.
What did you say?
I'm sorry. I'm a teacher.
I was invited.
I lent this tear bag to Ms. Hiyori.
Actually, Kanamin forgot her makeup
tools.
I yawned a lot.
Really?
I was wet when I met you in the
morning.
I don't know if it's eye drops.
It's a new one.
It's embarrassing.
I was sleepy and yawned a lot.
So, I lost my makeup.
I fixed it and I heard an angel's voice
saying,
Please give me sparkling eyes.
So, I lent it to her.
It's sparkling.
You're cute today.
Thank you.
Let's welcome the next guest.
Next, we have Ms. Sudaki.
Atsumori.
Thank you.
She is the guest of the day.
Ms. Sudaki.
Thank you.
What is the point of today's video?
The point of today's video is...
bangs.
Yes, bangs.
And ponytails are very cute.
Yes, they are.
Very cute.
Do you have any tips for ponytails?
I do.
What is it?
Thank you for watching.
That's...
Did you do it yourself?
I've been doing it for 10 years.
What are your shoes in teres?
Don't pull it too hard!
It hurts.
This is another special guest.
Shall we call her?
An-san!
Hello.
I'm An-san's guest.
How do you feel now?
I feel like...
I have the same hairstyle as Aki-chan's
birthday party.
But I changed my hairstyle to a bun.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
After this, we have a video of us in
spring.
And then, we have a video of us in
November.
Are you still nervous?
Not at all.
It's amazing.
I'm looking forward to it.
We will show you various things.
We will show you cute and beautiful
things.
See you in the next video.
The costumes are so cute.
I feel like I'm going to get married.
Oharu is going to get married.
It's so beautiful.
I raised her so well.
Let's go see it.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching.
The back that goes to the future, the
eyes that look at the future
Because it's too bright
I'm scared
I can't say I'm crying
Caramel is very high-class, aren't
they?
I have something to say.
What is it?
If you enjoyed watching our video,
and if you think we are the cutest in
the world,
please subscribe to our channel and
like this video!
Please leave a comment!
Bye bye!
Oh, I see.
You are so cute!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you!
You are so cute!
You are so good!
What?
I was moved!
I'm moved by your eyes.
I was moved by your eyes.
Thank you!
The end of love.
Throw me your soaring voice
Let's go!
up and down, let's keep it up for a
lifetime
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Please support us.
Thank you for your support.
I have gotten on the bus
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'll do my best!
Bye bye!
I'm going to be 20 today.
I'm going to be the first 20-year-old.
I'm going to cry because my stomach
hurts.
I'm nervous because it's my first time
to be on a live show.
I'm nervous. I'm going to cry.
I feel like I know more about the
people who practice in the studio.
Thank you! I'll do my best!
I'll give you a hint.
Kanamin, Miria, Dokan, Haruka, Aki,
Mirori, Super Tokimeki Advertising Club,
Rock'n'Roll!
The first one is the first one.
The second one is the second one.
The third one is the fourth one.
The fourth one is the fifth one.
Welcome to your spring!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
So cute.
The cake is so cute.
It's so cute.
Look. Chocolate.
There it is!
Thank you!
I thought you were going to do it like
this.
I was going to do it like this.
I want you to do it on the screen.
Can I?
Can I do it?
I have a mission.
I'm sorry.
Thank you!
What's this?
It's a balloon!
It was fun. It was a strange feeling.
I could see everyone.
It was fun to be with you.
I really want to do it.
The time stops.
The time stops at the third verse.
I can't help it.
Thank you for your commitment.
I heard it for the first time in the
rehearsal.
Really?
I'm glad.
Thank you.
I'm going to prepare for the birthday
party of Julia.
Next, Julia's birthday party.
Thank you.
That's all I said at the live.
Well...
I'll do my best to enjoy myself and
grow up.
Thank you very much.
I love cake.
I'll do my best.
I remember the reason for my wandering
So that I can laugh even when it rains
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain sparkle
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain sparkle
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano